Personal Info

- <u> LinkedIn</u>
- % GitHub
- Iran Tehran

Fatemeh Marzoughi (Saba)

Front-end Developer React & React-Native

Education

(Sep 2017- Dec 2021)

Diploma: Bachelor of Computer Engineering (Software)

University: Islamic Azad University, Tehran-Central branch

Summary

I'm a front-end developer with 2 years of full-time experience and 3 years of self-studying in this field. I have started my journey in programming since my entrance to the university. I have experience working with design patterns, OOP, functional programming, REST-API, React, React-Native on both iOS and Android, electron on Mac and Windows operating systems, etc. I'm ready for my new role and challenges.

Interests

- Developing mobile applications (esp. using React-Native)
- Increasing my backend skills (Go-lang)

Skills

React, React Native, iOS, Android, Git, Electron for desktop apps, TestFlight, Local Storage, Native-Base, Jest, HTML 5, CSS 3, SASS, web design, user experience (UX), JavaScript, Strapi CMS, TypeScript, Redux, Agile/Scrum team, REST-API, APIs, Design, Postman, patterns, functional and classbased React components, OOP, Collaborative environment, Mobile development, code review, Problem solving, GraphQL

Work Experiences

UniPlato: Mid-Level Front-End Developer Australia (Remote), Aug 2022 – May 2023, Visit Project

Brought the "Coffee" platform to its next level by building its

- desktop Mac Application using Electron and released over 20 versions of the app to TestFlight.
- Increased the usability of the code by building over 15 pixelperfect, responsive, and clean components.
- Brought over 20 new features with demos to the platform by communicating with team members and using REST-API, web sockets, and working with both functional and classbased components.
- o Improved the stability of the platform by reviewing new team members' codes.
- Upgraded the platform by refactoring the old code structures of 2 old modules and bringing them back to the project.
- Comfortel: Mid-Level Front-End Developer Russia (Remote), Dec 2021 - May 2022, Visit Project
 - Increased the usability of the "Techpal" platform by releasing its desktop app on 3 operating systems (Windows, Mac, and Linux) using Electron and its Android app using React-Native.
 - Refactored and added over 10 features to a flutter application named Smart Home.
- Open Source and Freelancing: Front-End Developer Tehran (Remote), Apr 2020 – Dec 2021, Visit Project
 - "MyPlayer" is an open-source React-Native project using TypeScript, available on both iOS and Android which is a Video and Audio player with over 20 features on it.